Guide to the Kristin Bedford photographs, 1930s-2018 RL.10156
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cruise Night, 2014-2018; 3.0 Linear Feet 3 boxes 68 photographic prints 13x19 (34) and 17x22 inches (34)
  - Handling prints, 2014-2018; .5 Linear Feet 1 box 34 photographic prints 13 x 19 inches
    - Santa Fe Springs, Loyal Alliance Car Club, Santa Fe Springs Swap Meet, Santa Fe Springs, California, 2016 September 3 (Box 13, Image RL.10156-P-0169)
    - I Did It My Way, Las Vegas, Nevada, 2015 October 10 (Box 13, Image RL.10156-P-0170)
    - Dorian, Emotions Car Club, Bellflower, California, 2017 November 26 (Box 13, Image RL.10156-P-0171)
    - Los Angeles River, Los Angeles, California, 2015 December 27 (Box 13, Image RL.10156-P-0172)
  - Exhibit prints, 2014-2018; 1.5 Linear Feet 2 boxes 34 photographic prints 17 x 22 inches
    - Inkjet prints from the series "Cruise Night" (Box 14, Box 15)
      RL.10156-P-0105 to RL.10156-P-0138